[Music]
[Applause]
thanks for coming out here to meditate
with me master yario poof but I have no
idea why you only meditate with
younglings it's no problem Sonic I just
love helping the babies with their
meditation training and it's not because
they meditate with their eyes closed so
they can't see me checking out their
tight little boties how long have you
been a pad one again 58 years that's
pretty hot haha want to go inside and
drink blue milk
together Sonic the Jedi Council is
requesting an audience with your fat
cheeks damn it y poof didn't the Council
ban you from mid 18 with the young LS no
okay they did please don't tell on me
yippi I hope today is the day Master
Yoda grants me the rank of jet die
Knight you wanted to see me master yodok
indeed stole a holocron from the Jedi
archives some [__] did was it to said
Lord that's what we wanted to talk to
you about youngling wait having a force
Vision I am wants me to go through ma
Windu's pocket
what the hell you think I stole the
goddamn H run no the force does it's
nothing personal Master Wu any one of us
Jedi could have stolen the holocron we
all need to be treated as equal suspects
no just Master Wu much Darkness I sense
in him darkness is it because I'm black
y do you want your triangle through my
pockets because I'm black no not try
only do do or do not there is no try so
you going look through my pockets this
what you saying yep more susceptible to
the influence of the dark side black
people are and surely you do have
scientific explanations to back up those
claims witnessed at firsthand I did
while backing to the Jedi Temple this
morning for work no you did not you
[__] yes [__] your mother last
night I did does that mean I'm closer to
the Light Side since I'm white no it
means you have to parents over this
meeting is got somewhere to be I do
butth we have to act fast if we are to
recover the stolen holocron oh yeah I
forgot your brother turned to the dark
side no youi manic is a proud knight of
the order caught him on a CCTV cam in
the archives we did stealing a Jedi
holocron he
was oh hey manic want to come help me
sort these secret Jedi holocron no
thanks I would rather kill you and then
take it for
myself
you did it baby now you can hand over
that artifact to your Evil's master and
take over the whole ass Galaxy with me
Daddy rules alone [__] but I'll keep
you around just because Daddy needs
someone to Lug around his massive green
balls turn it off I can't watch anymore
that's good because they have sex for
like 45
minutes we are under attack but who
would dare Bond the Jedi Temple with us
in it's be my player dressed in planning
to kill us all his oh [__] look at all
of those Star Destroyers is he going to
use the force to launch them all towards
the temple building not if anything to
say about it I
have Master Yoda you did it you stop the
Starships all by yourself no did
absolutely nothing I did Bart be stopped
all of the ships by himself you play
with me but what about the pressure that
blew off all of your clothes embarrassed
I was blew the clothes right off my body
myself I did now run fly to the planet
of Tatooine and defeat your brother
before it's too late be gone the BART Li
War
has
Amazing
Grace
sweet on a mission are you you know you
have a pretty big ass for a pad one I'm
starting to see why the ji Masters
refuse to promote you to the rank of
Knight it's so they can keep you here at
the temple day in and day out so they
can watch that ass pce up and down the
Halls like cranberry jelly he he and he
right thought Jedi weren't supposed to
think such things I look like I give a
[__] now tell me fat blue man have you
ever heard the story of Uncle Chuck yeah
he's my uncle well do you know he's also
been my secrets with Apprentice for 2
weeks you are lying my uncle has a
double-bladed lightsaber and when he
activates one side it's blue have you
ever seen him activate the other side oh
my God and so the flowers of doubt have
been
planted this is Uncle Chuck's room and
over there is his double-bladed
lightsaber next to his pot art
stash have you ever seen him activate
the other
side no my heart doesn't want to believe
it so but this Blood Red blade can only
mean one thing my very own Uncle Chuck
is Bartle be Monclair of Dresden Sith
Apprentice so my brother is innocent I
have to report this to the
council Uncle Chuck is it true that you
turned to the dark side
that's
so
theen as if I would ever join you when
the council hears about this
they I see well played Uncle what would
you have me to First my
master for a
long what's going on in here me Lord he
didn't
say you was merely ttin the CH for when
y came under your ruin oh really because
it sounded like you were taking him as
an apprentice to other throny perhaps I
heard wrong go fet me a slice or two of
blueberry cheesecake from the Cheesecake
Factory on nahu and if I see you talking
to that blue cutie papy again it will
Mark your
doom
well Bounty Hunter I'm sure I don't have
to remind you of our agreement you
didn't tell me he was a Jedi I may have
to ask you to pay double for this job
surely that is a small order for someone
who owns 9
32,400 and 50 star systems double the
credits uhuh that's no problem and for
the record it's
93241 star systems then the job goes
on
[Music]
the blue one has come damn it brother
it's time you return the holocron that
you stole you can't order me around
youngling you are not even a Jedi Knight
shut up why don't you come down here and
make me don't make me get out of the
Starship do it [__] this is your last
horning I'm going to get down if you
don't give it back do it [__]
okay fine you asked
for sure you want to do this big blue I
don't want to embarrass you in front of
my sexy slave [__] I'm not as weak as I
once was bro just yesterday I took on
all 12 members of the Jedi Council at
the same time and beete their ass then
this should be
fun
we
[Music]
go I'll
take it's to save the
[Music]
[Applause]
mess with the manic get treated like a
Hispanic oh no it's bounty Hunter manic
he's going to take him away take my
advice L you never want to get between a
bounty hunter and his prey go on and
take him Bounty Hunter he is yours to do
with as you please after all I already
got what I want yours smt for a Jedi now
get to move on fat boy you got to date
with a SI Lord and by date I mean you're
about to be [__] raped by Bartle
B I took the
lead I don't suppose there's any chance
you can pull over on the side of the
hypers space Lane so I can pee listen
bud I'm not too fond of taking orders
from the dark lord of the Sith but $20
is
$20 hey do you want to stop by The
Cheesecake Factory on NAU before I drop
you off might as well do something fun
before you get chained up at bartleby's
secret love hotel in the mustar
system
[Music]
okay
howdy Miss two slices of your finest
space cheesecakes to go please Sonia is
that useless why are you working at a
Cheesecake Factory oh hey Sonic I didn't
expect to ever see you again after the
Jedi took you from our family to raise
you and their [__] up cult you might
want to find a speeder and Tall ass I
hear barle be is doing everything in his
power these days to get his hands on you
we were just on our way to see him you
were she Ram found him in the middle of
a light a duel in the remote SS of TN on
the first day of the BART will be Wars
how did you manage that he farts really
loud defeat me in battle today you might
but the war you will not win shut the
[__] up you already tried to stop me and
failed because you are green like my
[__] it is time for you to die wait
please become your new Apprentice I will
suck your balls and destroy the Galaxy
for you I will oh I'm sorry but I think
my Apprentice just
arrived oh the adjudicators have finally
arrived and I see that you brought me my
cuit I brought you your designated
Bounty now hand over the credits no I'd
rather not no way it ain't going down
like this the Bounty money would go to
the one who brought the bo for me am I
not the one who put up the bounty in the
first place the way I see it and the one
who cruy captured his ass and you are
better too no different than the single
PL toilet paper that drags along my
crusty ass go Force
fat step right up Uncle shuck now it's
your turn to be farted out the
window F your bch I knew it you were
conspiring with my [__] in your bedroom
weren't you luckily my [__] is smart
now I'm going to have to spank you
really the hero must rise and defy to
save the Galaxy from Eternal
Night with light and hand sh fa
his be evil it starts to show the battle
rages on
gy fight alone you think you can defeat
me with a lightsaber that cheap it's not
even
gold holy [__] B leby is using the force
to fly away I didn't even know you could
do that wait he's coming back oh no he's
dropping him from 10,000 ft in the
air Uncle why is his lightsaber green
but not the usual kind I've never seen
such a beautiful lightsaber color like
that before
that's
it's similar to
American it's the most
expensive
ofid stop right there we are not going
to let you take our brother fools your
brother never was yours he was always
mine
no it can't be true all this time you've
been Bartleby secret
Apprentice well done my beach very well
done with a ji Temple destroyed no one
will be able to stop me from Conquering
the remaining star systems indeed my
love as always my fat ass is yours to do
with as you please well said Sonic the
Hedgehog why don't you take take a peek
in that holr old
[Music]
man I might be gay but I'm always a man
of my word and now and My [__] are
going to get in this Escape pod and fire
away to ad where we will be we to one
another you're just going to leave us
trapped behind this Ray Shield forever
gracious no my sister we already set
course for the ship in just a few
minutes it's going to fly right into the
sun with all of you on board consider it
an act of Mercy from my Lord
[Music]
lover in a galaxy far far away yeah I
master you let the way yeah but
theing so
mean I feel this
closing oh no oh it's like show
down you just got to fight it's time to
go B Be You Won't Prevail your is got
the for
never
yeah sonic twins so fast fighting each
other Shadows they
cast manic took a stand Sonic took
a but in the end it was Sonic who Wasau
in
the all in the face of the but the force
was no match for the Evil
Within as clo BL up as the St destroy
ands
nowfe fell and B will be
winds Shadows of the
trail Galaxy
pain B Be Rings Darkness Falls like w no
hope
inside as Eagle claims this world
[Applause]
be the force of Darkness now the
galaxies